safetyissues.com 2005-12-12

# Safety Issues Privacy Policy

**Our Online Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our site.

**This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

 **Personal Identification Information**  
We will never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user (such as, for example, your full name, street address, telephone number, credit card number, or e-mail address) to any third party without having received your permission. We may request personal identification information from you in connection with your use of, or participation in, our surveys, quizzes, games, forums, subscription registrations, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions, visitors' requests for products or services, or additional information, and in connection with other activities, services or resources we may make available. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us.

If you do provide us with personal information, we may use it to conduct the activities described above. If you identify yourself to us by sending us an e-mail with questions or comments, we may use your personal information to respond to your questions or comments, we may file your comments for future reference, or we may discard the information after we have reviewed it.

We may also contact you to confirm your registration and regarding changes to the Safetyissues.com Site's Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy.

If you give us your permission, we may also use personal identification information for internal or external marketing and promotional purposes. On occasion, for example, we may send you e-mails to introduce a product or service that we think might be of interest to the users of our sites. For us to obtain your permission to send you this information, we will give you an opportunity to "opt-in" at the time our request for your personal information is made. If you do "opt-in," you may choose to "opt-out" at any time, even after you have provided personal information, but following the procedures set forth below at the end of this Privacy Policy. Please note, however, that under certain circumstances, if you initially do not choose to "opt-in," or if you later "opt-out," you may not be eligible for certain benefits for which a name, e-mail address, telephone number, or other personal identification information is needed.

We have the following exceptions to these policies: We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Safetyissues.com site, or a physical threat to you or others.

Please note that if you give out personal information online—for example, through a message board or chat room—that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users' privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you may choose to post on our site.

 **Privacy of Children**  
We understand that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users. We urge all parents to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information online.

Safetyissues.com has adopted the following special policies to protect the privacy of users who are under 13 years old:

No information may be submitted on or to Safetyissues.com by users under 13 without consent of their parent or guardian.   
Users under 13 may not register with Safetyissues.com on their own. A user under 13 may be registered only by a parent or guardian.   
If a user under 13 wins a contest for which such user is eligible, notification and prizes will be sent to their parent or guardian who initially registered the user.   
No personal information concerning users under 13 will be used for any marketing or promotional purposes, either inside or outside Safetyissues.com.   
Use of Cookies  
We do not use "cookie" technology to collect information from or about you.

 **Choice/Opt-Out**  
If you "opt-in" to receive information from Safetyissues.com or others, you can change your mind later. If, at any time, you would like to stop receiving such information, you can let us know by sending an e-mail stating your preference to webmaster@Safetyissues.com.

 **Your Acceptance of These Terms**  
By using our site you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
